{
    "subject": "resource/UD_Melilla",
    "predicate": "ontology/ground",
    "object": "resource/Estadio_Municipal_\u00c1lvarez_Claro",
    "human_readable": "UD Melilla is grounded at Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9622165560722351,
            "question": "Is Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro located in Melilla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983954191207886,
            "question": "Where is UD Melilla grounded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7787694931030273,
            "question": "Which team uses Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro as their home ground?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7618312835693359,
            "question": "What type of facility is Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5985937118530273,
            "question": "What are some famous matches that have been played at Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38374826312065125,
            "question": "Does UD Melilla have a strong fan base?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38067659735679626,
            "question": "What is the name of the stadium where UD Melilla plays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37030544877052307,
            "question": "Where would you go to watch a UD Melilla game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3200984001159668,
            "question": "Does UD Melilla play professional football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04125506430864334,
            "question": "Can you find other sports teams that use this stadium?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=UD Melilla is grounded at Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4802_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does UD Melilla play professional football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4802_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you go to watch a UD Melilla game?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4802_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the stadium where UD Melilla plays?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4802_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4802_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I can confirm that:\n\n{'output': 'yes'} \n\nThe information in the documents indeed supports the triple \"UD Melilla is grounded at Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro\". Specifically, document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4802/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt mentions that \"Ud Melilla plays its home matches at Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro\", and other documents further confirm this as the home stadium of UD Melilla."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query \"UD Melilla is grounded at Estadio Municipal \u00c1lvarez Claro\" is supported by the documents, which state that Ud Melilla plays its home matches at this stadium."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}